Good morning, it
's 9:00 in the morning and we're
leaving for
a holiday
in
Tuscany.
[music]
So, we're about to go to Tuscany and the
participants of this holiday will be
me, Thiago, my brother, my dad,
my dad's partner, my grandfather, my
grandmother, my dad's partner's mother
.  We are half of 1000. Oh, and the
most important participant of this
holiday will be Frida, aka the
little dog I gave
to my dad last year.  We're almost all ready
except
obviously my brother.  We'll spend this
week's vacation in Tuscany
and bye.  I'm going to Tuscany with my
little willy, he's
saying, with my grandfather.   I thought so too
.
How cool is Maranza.  Go Maranza.  I've
already finished packing my suitcase, I
just need to put the last few things in.
So, our starting cars
are my dad's C3 and my C3 that
we are preparing.  We still have to
fill in here.  I'm just telling you that they have to
stay there, that is, there has to be room
for a dog and two of my
grandparents' suitcases.  Here are the other participants,
Frida
and the ondina.
Come on, let's turn on the air now, stay
calm.
So guys, here we are, we're about to
leave.  Here we have Giacomo, in front
we have the INS car, so the
old one.  [laughter]
Yes, Madonna, poor
Frida, put her in your arms.
Let's get going.  I have to buy petrol
because I have 35 km of autonomy.  Arrived in
Parma.
In Parma.
In Parma.  Eh, we're stopping in Onesia to
eat something.  Nothing, after eating
we set off again on our journey of
hope.  Ah, there's
really been a lot of fuss up until now, eh, but I
'm
still here, er, I'm really the
biggest complainer on the
face of the earth.  I mean, I
like to complain, I like to do
things while complaining.  Laugh,
laugh.  Bye my love.  Go, run,
run, run, run.  Laugh, look.
Good.
Everyone gathered together.
I'm eating a pasta ragù that
Thiago hasn't eaten,
usually already sweet.  Okay.  Show me
subscribe to the channel.
Ate.  We are heading to the
location.  We are heading
towards Supereto.
Guys, after 17 hours
and 56 minutes of travel we arrived.  It doesn't
seem real to me.  It's 6 o'clock for the poor thing.  There
's a ping pong table here.  This is
the entrance with everyone, what are
those called?  Are you pressing us, are
you lending us?  Another large table with a
lounge and the swimming pool finally.  Darling,
now we have to put on our swimsuits and
take a dip.  Here is the kitchen.
Here is a first room with this beautiful
canopy bed.  The only thing that's
scaring me is that there's no air
conditioning.  I hope that's
an air because we'll die of heat if it's
not.  A bathroom.  Then there is another
small room with a sofa and two beds.
Here is another room with some sofas,
a desk.  Over here there's another bathroom
and another room I think I'll
get this nice room.
In fact, I'll put my phone here so it
remains my room.  Theoretically
there is a part above that should
open with this key.   I
think.  Okay.  I honestly don't know how,
but I managed to get in.  Here there is a
second kitchen with a fireplace.  This
kitchen is a little bigger than the
previous one.  And on this side there is
a living room, a very large room with
three beds.  Oh God, a fan.  Oh God,
another bed.  Obviously, there's
another room on this side.  I still don't know
how many rooms there are, honestly.  And here's
a bathroom.  Up here
we're preparing the aperitif.  Tiago is
there with his towel.
HI.
HI.  [music]
And dad is taking a bath.  In
the pool.   You
have to wear a swimsuit in the swimming pool.
You're naked.
So, it's 8:30 or
so anyway.  This was Thiago's pasta that he did
n't want to finish, so now I'll eat
two bucconi.  In the meantime, they're
setting the table over there.  Happy birthday
to you, happy birthday [sing]
to you, happy birthday
Massi, happy birthday
to you
Vitalnato.
Let's watch cartoons with Frida
and here we'll all eat.  I was just finishing
watching Temptation Island.   They
all went to sleep and I
put Tiaghino to sleep.  Now I'm going to finish
watching it, then I'm going to collapse too because it's really
late and I'm incredibly sleepy.
I have to finish watching it.  I mean, do you realize
what you're eating now?
A biscuit.
Good morning.
Good morning dear.
Let's go outside.  However, the only smart ones
are the young and the old, the
middle-aged ones.  I didn't understand
why not.  We are the only ones.  Give me a
kiss.
It's a chicken.
The rooster clucks and
clucks.  But
why?  But why [snorting] are
the galls crowing now and we
woke up galls?  Yes. But
where is it?   Hate
.  Honey, we were talking about you.
Cool,
were you good?  Hi love, here you are.
[laughter]
Where were you?  Where were you?  [laughter] Where were you?   Where were
you?  Where were you?  Where were you?
Jumped on me to wake me up.   Did
you wake up?  [laughter]
Ah,
there you go.
Don't punch him, though.
Good morning.  [scream]
Hello love.   I
'm coming down for breakfast.  Dad.  Hey, are
you moving?
Oh, what a drag!  But I'm going to have
breakfast.  By the way, my grandmother made me
hot tea about half an hour ago,
but I forgot to come downstairs,
so I think it's probably cold now
and she'll be mad at me.  Plum cake
with hot tea for the boys.  Thiago is
playing with a paddle.  I don't know what
your nephew is doing.
Mom, little
space.  [laughter]
Check it out, guys.  One,
2, 3, go!
Let's put this on Thiago so we can go in.
No,
come on dad.  Oh,
I inflate that.  Come on, popes, please.
You have to pump everyone up.  Go, go
to me too.
But how many things are you filming?
[laughter]
Big Brother.
Go grandpa.
No, I don't [laughter] [ __ ]
hour [music] later.
What did you eat?
Little bulls.
Tortellini.  Where is Frida?  I closed the
door because it brought a bit of
wind.  Everyone's eating here.
Pasta with ragù.
Tiago and I ate
tortellini instead because we had
already eaten the batter yesterday.  I think
I'll put Tiaghino to sleep soon because he's
very very very tired.  This morning I
woke up very early.
So, I put Tiaghino to sleep,
and I took a bath, but it's a bit
hot, so it's nice.  Only
I'm here in the shade, one because I was
very hot and two because Thiago is sleeping here
, so if he wakes up I can hear him.  The
others are in the pool.  Now I'm
changing Thiago's swimsuit, come
here.
HI.
So, we're having an
aperitif.  They made guacamole
which is delicious.  You're so in love with
some pepper lime chips.  So, here
is the preparation by cutting salami.
Instead of here.  So, what is it here
?
So these are so first we
start beautiful blonde with the aubergines that
Londina cut and Francesca fried.
Then Londina cut the
washed peppers, chopped them and Francesca fried them.
Londina cut the potatoes and
Francesca fried them.  Londina cut the
onions and Francesca Fritto and
lastly the tomato.  [laughter] Tomato
Dinunzio.  Hurray.  But these are
French fries.   This
is a French fry, but it's
very hot.  Now we have to blow a
lot.  It's
small.   Okay
.
Anyway, everyone's eating
[laughter] except me because I was very
full from the aperitif.
Then Thiago and I went for a
walk, right?
Where did we go for a walk?
In the house violet which is very long
with all the cypresses.  It was
beautiful.  Now we took a
shower that also washed our hair and that's it
.  Now let's play
ball, shall we?  And you also got the
hiccups during all this.  But how
sweet are these children?   They
love each other
very much.  How much do you love Frida?
Very, very much.
And how much does Frida love you?   To
the moon.   To
the moon.  You are beautiful
together, you know that?   My
friends have all abandoned me.  They
all went to sleep.  It's midnight.
I'm using my phone as a flashlight
because it's completely dark outside.  I'm
finishing watching the episode of
Temptation.  I'm going to sleep too
because tomorrow morning we'll definitely
wake up early and I have
like a month's worth of sleep to catch up on, I can't take it
anymore.  But I have to finish watching it, we'll
catch up tomorrow.  It's 7:00 in the
morning.
A mosquito bit you
in the eye.  I don't know why he
woke up now, but I'm dying of
sleep.
Let's go to the sea.  Where are we going?   They
rimigliano.  I'm going to the beach.   I do
n't even remember what
this beach is called anymore.  I just know that we
have to walk a bit through the woods to
get there.
Life,
my love, love, love.
Hi guys.
Guys,
the sand is rising.  You can't take it anymore.  But you're
not even walking.
What a [ __ ].
Holy Mary,
look at yourself.
Oh, how beautiful!
Oh, the Madonna!  One
seems like a mirage to me.
[music]
We've taken a billion baths in the
sea, both with Frida and without, with
Thiago, with everyone, and I'm exhausted.
My hair obviously got wet.  and I will
wash them in the evening.  I think we'll
go back soon for something to eat because he's
dead tired.   I'll
explain it to you there.  Beautiful and serene.  This used to be
my towel until
Frida decided to take
aim at it.  What are you eating, love?
Hulk Pasta.
Hulk pasta.  Well,
I'm really in a
pitiful state.  We just got home,
I'm really tired, I just took a really
long shower with Thago,
while my grandparents went to
get the bacon, because my dad
can make pasta carbonara, so
I'll wait a little before
eating, I mean this hair that I
absolutely have to wash, but since
we're definitely going to the
pool this afternoon, I'll wash it this evening.  There is the shadow.
So, this fat guy with a
17-month-pregnant belly made an
incredible carbonara with my
brother who, for the first time in 4
days, was able to look up
from his phone.  Assuming this
type of post, she could also go.  I
would say the vote.  I'll give you my vote.  No,
seven from seven.
We gave 6 plus 6 and a half.
No, seven I seven.
Oh, even [ __ ].
I ate it.
I ate it.  [laughter]
I ate my grandfather's food.  I ate it the next
day at 6:15.  I slept until now
.  Me and Thiago for about 2 and
a half hours, I think.  Now I'm going to take a dip
in the pool.
2 3 [music]
Well done
then.
Oh no, this is the cut.
The men went to get
the meat to make the
barbecue.
But as soon as I got
ugly, I braided my hair.
Obviously I took a
very long shower
together with this pest back here, I
washed my hair, I made
these braids so tomorrow morning,
Madonna, this horrible braid I
wake up with wavy hair and my
grandmother has prepared some
incredible things that are, I swear,
delicious.  Now I'll show them to you.
Guys, one of those
galbanino fadelfi puff pastry and cooked ham.
Guys, these are amazing things, I
swear.  I could eat 800 of them. Some
salami just for you,
eh?
Get the salami just for you.
And you don't eat them,
huh?  After.  Look what a mess we have.
That is, what do we have?
Yeah, but still, guys, you're
exaggerating, huh.  [music]
But we have 800 more meats to eat.
No, I eat this.
Giacomo and Thiago are eating
the hamburger without the bun because why not?   He
ate it a little with bread, then
realized it was falling apart a little and said,
"Okay, I'll eat the meat."  So, what's
this Thiago burger like?
Good or very good?  Very good, I'm
going to sleep.  It's
midnight and I don't remember if I showed you
[laughter] what I
ate, but I think I did because my
dad grilled.  I ate the
salamella, actually I have a lot of
antipasti, so I didn't eat the
tagliata, Florentine steak and everything else they
had cooked.  I'm going to sleep with
these braids.   I
'm indecent.  We'll talk tomorrow
morning.  Good morning.
So, it's 9:30.  He woke up
at 7:30 and nothing, now I'm going to have
a quick breakfast, then I'll join them at the
pool.  Hi,
where are you going?
Look, it goes against the water.  Oh, no.
So, I put on my swimsuit and by the
time I put it on, Thiago had come out
of the water.
Where are you going?
By bike.
Go cycling.   Okay
,
we can go to the pool later if you want.  I'm
copying myself.   I'm
copying you.   I need a
great idea.   Does
going to the
pool afterwards sound like a great idea?
What are you doing?  Did a mosquito bite you?
No, because I peed myself
.
What are you saying?  You're kidding,
right?
Already.  Is Thiago a joke or is it the truth?
It is
the truth.
Pull up your shirt, let me see.  No,
you haven't done it yet.  Come on, let's do this
quickly.  So, friends,
it's Luna.  We took a few
dips in the pool.  I'd like to show
Tiagino, but he's dancing around the
house without any clothes on.
Go, take people back.
Frida,
where are you going?
Ready.
Tiago, Hulk's pasta is ready.
Oh good right away.
We ate pasta, ham and
melon and Thiago Hulk pasta, aka
Hulk.  [laughter]
You're turning into the Hulk.
Look, he's turning into the Hulk.  Look at
the party already getting green eat
become
here.  There are so many flies that I
'm not living in peace.  The
next fly that comes at me I'll
kick dad.  That is, he told me that
with the ut they were leaving.  It is not true.
Hi friends, I got ready, I put on my
makeup, I did a get ready
on TikTok and I just dressed
Thiagoalro too.  What is it, we're
going out soon.
I have to do my grandmother's hair.  Hi
guys, we're going to dinner at this
place.  Where?  Castagneto Carducci
source of Fuiano
farmhouse.  We will take you with us.  He's
recording my brother who isn't very
happy about recording.  He is not happy.   Come on
.  Well.
Where are you Thiago?
Traore.
Wow.
Oh.
Tiago is eating pasta.  [crying] You ca
n't show this to anyone.   Are
you eating?  Okay.
With what?
A potato stuffed with purple potatoes
and then some cheese, I don't remember.
You come.
He's hyperactive today.  Would you communicate with
stickers?
My brother would like to communicate
[music] with stickers in
normal life too.  That is, he is talking and
would like to send it on WhatsApp.  I
use this TikTok so much.
Ah, what kind of person in life would you like to
spawn a sticker.  While you're talking, you
imagine yourself looking for something like the stick.
I do it, that is, anyway, limit.   Ah
, miid.
Guys, I'm sleepy, I want to go
home.   Ninth
.
Good morning, I look like a lion.  So,
friends, eh, I don't remember where I
left you in the evening, honestly.
When we got home it was
very late, that is, for Thiago it was very
late.  That is, it means 11:30.
Look who's arrived,
look who's arrived.
Bye my love.
In the morning, he didn't wake up at 7:00,
but woke up at 8:30.  It's a great
achievement, even though I fell
asleep at 2:00.  Oh, how sleepy!
Actually, nothing, now I'm going to do two
things I have to do on the computer.  Tio, I'll
make him watch a couple of cartoons and then we'll either
go to the beach or go to the pool.
So, we had breakfast, I don't think we're
going to the beach.  We'll stay by the
pool, then maybe we'll go to the beach
this afternoon.  Good morning.
Good morning.
At last.  We've all been awake for 2
hours.  You know it?  You're woken up at 8:00 am, that
's not my problem.
And why didn't you wake up?
I can sleep at least until 10.
What time did you fall asleep?
Moon.
I fell asleep later than you,
yet I woke up before you.
Ah, that's not good, sleep like that.   I
decided to wake up at 8:00.
They are costumes and now let's go.  By the
way, I'm getting nervous because I've been
trying to set up
a 96% TikTok since last night and I don't know how to
delete it, I mean, it won't let you delete it
or post it, so it's a bit of a hassle
honestly.  Tiago
[music]
is cold.  Liar.  We took a
dip in the pool.  It's
12:15 now and we should have lunch.  We're
leaving tomorrow.  So this is
actually our last day.
By the way, my dad said there were some
problems with
this house, but I'll explain them to you
better later.  Now let's have an aperitif
and then we'll eat
all the pasta.
Just pasta for us.  Just pasta.
So, we need to tell you all the
things that were wrong with this house,
so
then you
won't ask me for the link to this
Airbnb.
The location is beautiful,
the location is beautiful, the house is
wonderful, but
beautiful.  But then the fact is that
they said that each room had a
fan as there was no air
conditioning.  There were fans but they didn't
work.   They brought them to us
unassembled.
We had to assemble them ourselves on vacation, which
is not something you should do.
Then she even found
rotten water in the kettle.  Then
my bidet was broken, so every time
you opened it the bathroom would flood.
What is the pool?  Okay, the grill guys
, the grill is not done,
guys.  SPCH.  It's a very nice house,
so it has a certain cost, a certain
price.  The grill was greasy, dirty, and
dirty.  Well, then the pool, the
pool when we arrived, wasn't
very clear because obviously
they hadn't put any salt in it, they hadn't put any
chlorine in it,
and so they had to do maintenance
while we were here.
Eh, you don't do it, you don't do it, the whole
part of the cutlery,
the things, very clean, it
wasn't very clean.  I like it because
the house is very beautiful,
but in a house like that
one person can't manage the cleaning
and so
basically I don't see
from that point of view, right?  The post is
really wonderful because as you can see it is
beautiful, there are two apartments,
but it needs to be maintained much much
better, so we are sorry to tell you how
beautiful the location is, but maybe the guys.
So, here we are still eating
pasta sauce.  I can't take it anymore.  No,
I swear, I ate, we ate like
five times, move on to the sauce.
Exact.  I ate Yes, I understood.
Yesterday I ate Passa al sugo, the day before
yesterday Passa al sugo, [laughter] the day before yesterday
Passa al taglio di pasta.   Just
eat that.
We're Italian, it
's not true, but I eat a lot of
things.  And you only prepare this.
Why didn't you prepare?
Oh,
beautiful.  But I eat I love pasta.
I would eat pasta every day.
In fact, I'm eating pasta every
day.
Savory pie.  We want the savory pie
of the savory pie of the spinach soy.
But then but then you made the really good one.
Meat cut potatoes.
Many years ago.   I
don't need my specialties.
Eh, since you were looking I saw
you were looking it's good, it
's not good.
So, here guys we're playing
scala 40. These are my cards.  Oh,
can we connect live?
Come on, but a two.  But what kind of paper is it?
These are discarded.
In your opinion
[music] ca
n't you get off early.  But what's the point of going
down for now?
Then
the two were essential [music]
to take with scenes.  Play.
Come on, [music]
[music] sorry, dat.  So friends, I
've taken yet another swim, I mean, I'm no
longer really counting how many I
've taken.  Now I'm soaking wet
and in fact I need to dry myself
at least a little bit before I go out, I'm going to
buy Thiago some hamburgers
because tonight we're making him
hamburgers, so he'll be happy while we
eat the rest of the barbecue
we had left over from last time.  I have to
change.  So, here we are
continuing the grid for the second
time.  And where are my sausages?
There.  Why aren't you cooking them?  You have some
shipments.
No, actually I'm ribs.
Hey, I'm here.
And the salt after the salt.
No, they've already made the burger.
Now I'll show you what the hamburger looks like.
Health.  Well,
I guess.  Very good.  I took it, We
also took the French fries.  I'm here
.   She
made him French fries.
So, I'm eating the third
rib.
Sorry guys, but they eat with their
hands for me.  Now I'm waiting for the
sausage, but I don't want the skewers,
I just want this and sausage.  You hear
my father's insults starting in three
2 1 It was
not said that you wanted the shipments.
Eh, but I don't want them.
Let's go shopping.
But then I didn't ask you for them.
We were going shopping.  So
why did Dad take them?   I'll take the
skewers.  But who
eats them?  Did your dad take them?  HI.
But that's not true.  Good morning.   I
forgot to say
goodnight yesterday.  I'm up until 2:00 in the morning
drying my hair,
that is, washing and drying my hair which
is now like this because I didn't have the
courage to straighten it.  Now we're having
breakfast with
And then after, do you know where we're going back?  Let's go back
to Cadoraggo.
In Cadorago.
But then I want to go to the
swimming pool.
Eh, I know.
Let's see if we can get one last
dip before heading back to Cadorago
in 8,000°C temperatures.  Tell me, my love.  I'm
hiding a penny from Gii.
You're hiding a penny from Gii with
the fan pointed at 8,000° 1000°.
I managed to get my hair out.   Here I am
.  I did it
and we're leaving soon to go back.
Do you want to go for one last swim or do
you want to leave right away?
Eh, I want to leave right away.
Do you want to leave right away?
Yes. That's
fine.
Please, we'll
update later.  We are officially
leaving.  We've already put all our
luggage away.  I, this hair, guys, is
unworthy because it's so hot that
all the luggage is there.
Okay, guys, nothing, my video
ends here because our vacation
ends right now.
Now let's go.  Say hello to grandma.  Hello
everyone.   Say
hello.  Hello
grandpa.
Hi everyone.  Bye
bye
co,
bye.